前院里怎么有那么多巨型棒棒糖啊
Why there are giant lolipops all over the front yard?
怎么味道那么怪呢
And why they taste so bad?
因为是硬纸板做的 蠢蛋
Because they are made of cardboard, mouth breather.
世界需要梦想家 卢克
Hey, the world needs more dreamers, Luke
舔舐不息 梦想不止
Never stop licking things.
我知道很挫
I know it's lame,
可是去年答应了邻居们
but after last year we promised the neighbours
我们会把装饰弄得和谐一点
we would keep our decorations more family friendly.
我们连刻个南瓜都不行吗
We can't carve a pumpkin?
他们的请愿书写得十分有针对性
The petition was very specific.
每次万圣节 我们家装扮得最恐怖
Every Halloween, we have the best house.
去年 我的水平更上一层楼
Last year, I took things to a whole new level.
但显然对于某些孩子来说太恐怖了
But appearently it's too scary for some kids.
外加一个大人
And one adult.
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick-or-treat!
你们想要点糖吃吗
Would you like some candy?
是的
Yeah!
还是更想要这个呢
Or would you rather have this?
别装了 才吓不着你呢
Come on. You're fine.
我才不管别人说什么
I don't care what anyone says.
反正不是你害的那人心脏病发作
You did not give that man a heart attack.
谢谢
Thank you.
你根本就不吓人
I mean, you're not even scary.
我能抓点糖吗
Can I grab a little bit of this candy
给今晚看房的客户们吃
for my open house tonight?
可以 当然 可是
Uh, yeah, sure, but...
太有才了 在万圣节办开放参观
It's genius. An open house on Halloween.
当爹妈的无聊透了
Millions of bored parents,
平常忙着照看孩子 不出车祸
just trying to keep their... kids out of traffic.
现在他们可以脱身啦
Now they can get away from all that,
去参观一座好房子
And see a nice house.
什么叫我根本就不吓人啊
What do you mean, I'm not even scary?
我差点吓出一条人命来
I literally almost scared the life out of a man.
你就是把人家吓出了点白沫
You literally scared a little saliva
吓出了点尿
And a little urine out of him.
我每次看到猴子穿着人的衣服闹腾就这样
That happens to me every time I see a monkey wearing people clothes.
我相当吓人
I was plenty scary.
我的妆容可是专业等级的
I used professional-grade makeup.
说到点子上了 克莱尔 你太过了
That's the point, Claire. It was overkill.
你是那种
You're the kind of person
不化妆才吓死人的女人 再见
who can be twice as scary without wearing any makeup. Bye.
你记得去把装扮服取回来了 是吧
You remembered to pick up the costumes, right?
对的 放在那儿了
Yes, they're right over there.
太激动人心了
Very excited.
小卡减了不少肥
Cam has lost a lot of weight--
打住
No.
所以我们打算开个万圣节派对
So we're throwing a Halloween party
让全新的小卡粉墨登场
to debut the new him.
我将扮成斗牛士
I'll be dressed as a matador.
现在减了多少磅 30吗
Wh-what is it now, 30?
相当于我减掉了莉莉的重量[丢了]
So I've lost Lily.
莉莉去哪儿了
Where is lily?
-你 她没有跟你一起吗 -没
- Do you--you don't have her? - No.
她怎么会跟我在一起呢
Why would I have her?
-我又没把她装在口袋里 -小卡
- I don't have her in my pocket. - Cam?
皇冠头饰呢
What about the tiara?
我们没买
Uh, we didn't buy one.
你可以戴去年的
You can just use the one from last year.
我们变穷了吗
Are we poor?
不是 甜心 你用不着两个皇冠头饰啊
No, sweetheart, but you don't need two tiaras.
明年万圣节你换套服装怎么样啊
How about next Halloween you try a different costume?
不行 我必须扮公主
No. I have to be a princess.
每年都要吗 为什么
Every year? Why?
因为我妈妈是个公主
Because my mom's a princess,
你告诉我的
Just like you told me.
我和小卡都知道早晚有一天
Cam and I have always known that someday,
我们得和莉莉谈谈
we were gonna have to have the big talk with lily,
她妈妈的事
about who her mom was.
我 我们会找准时机
We--we were gonna pick the right time
一起跟她谈
and do it together,
严格按我们商量好的剧本上演
Carefully following an agreed-upon script.
然后有一天我累了
Then I got tired.
"她是人间天堂魔幻三界最漂亮的公主
"And she was the most beautiful princess in all the land.
剧终"
The end."
多少遍了啊
Again.
为什么泰勒的妈妈那么肥
Why is Tyler's mommy so fat?
那是因为她 她怀着个小宝宝
Oh, that's because she has-- she has a baby in her belly.
行了吧 晚安
Okay? Good night.
我妈妈也怀过我吗
Was I in my mom's belly?
莉莉 不许再问了 好吧
Lily, no more questions, all right?
快 快睡觉
Just--just go to sleep.
我妈妈现在在哪儿
Where's my mom now?
她在
Um, she's...
在遥远的国度
in a faraway land.
为什么
Why?
因为她是个公主
Because she's a princess.
并且她 很忙很忙
And she's... very, very busy.
好吧
Okay.
我以为她第二天早晨就忘了呢
I thought that she'd forget about it by the next morning.
反正我是忘了
I mean, I did.
我知道终究是要告诉小卡的
Oh, I knew I was gonna have to tell Cam,
他知道了肯定会很生气
and he was gonna be furious,
但我希望他能意识到更严重的问题
but I was hoping that he'd see the bigger issue.
我当时真的累惨了
You know, I was really tired.
小卡 你知道莉莉
Hey, Cam, you know this whole thing
今年又想打扮成公主吗
about Lily wanting to be a princess again?
我想 那可能是因为我让她相信
Well, I-I think it might be because I let her believe
-她妈妈是 -真是场噩梦
- her mother was-- - This is a nightmare.
-只是犯了点小错 -简直是灾难啊
- It was just a mistake. - More like a disaster.
他们送来的斗牛士服是按你的尺寸做的
They sent the matador costume in your size,
而公牛服按我的尺寸做的
and the bull costume in mine.
我没注意到
Oh. I didn't notice. Um...
穿着这件肥大的公牛服
Now no one's gonna see my bod
别人看不到人家的好身材了啦
in this bulky bull costume.
这个 真的是无心之过啦
It was--it was honestly a mistake.
听着 你也可以尝试你以前想试的造型
L-listen, um, you--you could do that other thing that you thought of.
你现在也可以穿那套
You could put on that gorgeous white suit
超美超合身的白色西服
that fits you so well now,
然后扮演洛克先生
and you could be Mr. Roarke,
让莉莉扮你的"小纹身"
and Lily could be your Tattoo.
不行 人家就要当公主
No! I have to be a princess!
但是莉莉 你去年就扮过公主了呀
Oh, but, Lily, you were a princess last year.
不行 你答应过我的 我就要当公主
No! You promised! I'm being a princess!
她为什么这么痴迷于公主
Why is she so obsessed with princesses?
怎么说呢
Well...
我们小时候也成天想当公主啊
Like we weren't at that age?
我是说
I mean...
我不是因为这罚单生气
I'm not mad about the ticket.
只是这是我第一次没能成功地
It's just the first time I couldn't charm my way
利用个人魅力免于处罚
Out of one of these things.
在我看来 这不是罚单问题
The way I see it, it's not a ticket.
而是社交问题
It's a conversation.
无意冒犯 但你根本不需要警笛
No offense. You don't need that siren.
你一下警车 别人就都停下来盯着看了
You could stop traffic just getting out of that squad car.
请给我你的驾照和车辆注册证
License and registration, please.
我
I, uh...
我对警察学校挺熟的
I'm no stranger to the police academy myself.
我看过全7部电影
Seen all seven of them.
先生 没人看过7部全辑
Sir, no one's seen all seven.
-上面的个人信息都准确吗 -是的
- Is this information accurate? - Yeah.
除了体重
Uh, except for the weight.
我以为他们是想知道我能举多重的东西
I thought they wanted to know how much I could curl.
我的技能日渐生疏了啊
I must be getting rusty with my moves.
技能 什么技能
Moves? What moves?
闪动我浅蓝色的媚眼
You know, flash the baby blues,
用奸笑迷惑她
hit 'em with the devilish grin.
紧急情况下 砸破车窗
In case of emergency, break glass
露出我迷人的酒窝
and bust out the dimple.
那不是天花留下的疤吗
Hey, isn't that one from the smallpox?
你当我100岁了啊 是水痘
'cause I'm 100. Chicken pox.
是什么留下的疤不重要
And it doesn't matter where it's from.
管用就行了
It always worked.
妈我回来了
Hey, mom.
曼尼 你怎么这么晚才从学校回来
Manny, why are you coming back from school so late?
我被叫到校长办公室去了
I got sent to the principal's office.
我要发电子邮件骂他去
Oh. I am sending him an angry e-mail,
因为我不知道什么时候
because I don't like when--
不不不 不是他的错
No, no, no. It's not his fault.
-你做错了什么事 -没有
- What did you do wrong? - Nothing.
就这样定了 我给他打电话
Oh, that's it. I'm calling him.
-我讨厌他故意 -不是故意的
- I hate when he tries to-- - Nothing on purpose.
下课时 在一场大考之前
It was between periods, right before this big test.
我在练习吉恩·凯利的舞步
I was clearing my mind by practicing
来排除杂念
some of my Gene Kelly dance moves.
-竟然真有人那样做 -没错
- As one does. - Right.
我的雨伞不小心勾到了火警警报
And my umbrella accidentally snagged the fire alarm.
校长以为我是故意这样做
The principal thought I did it on purpose
-为的是逃避考试 -但你不是
- so we'd miss the test. - But you didn't!
就这样 我要找他去
That's it! I'm going to his house!
妈 你千万别这样
Mom! You gotta stop doing this.
我不知道是不是因为怀孕
I'm not sure if it's the pregnancy,
当然 怀孕并不是你的错
which we both know isn't your fault...
但最近你总是很暴脾气
But lately you've been such a hothead.
我不是暴脾气 我是哥伦比亚人
I am not a hothead! I am Colombian.
我们这叫兴奋
We get excited.
我们国家长满了咖啡
My country is covered in coffee.
就像那个听错了你订单的星巴克店员
Just like the Starbucks girl
也被你泼的满身都是咖啡吗
when she got your order wrong?
半"咖灰" 无脂 "丝豆辣铁"
Half-caf, non-fat wet soy latte.
这很难听清吗
How hard is that to hear?!
不按常规思考的人不可能
You don't get to be 2-time nonconsecutive
两次夺得年度跨区域推销员称号的
district salesman of the year without thinking inside the box.
没错 我说的就是 按常规
That's right. I said "Inside."
知道为什么吗 因为当每个人
You know why? 'cause while everyone's
都试图打破常规时
chasing each other around outside the box,
你知道常规是什么吗
You know what the box is?
常规里空无一人
Empty.
现在我们又回到了正式的用餐室
Which brings us back to our formal dining room.
有什么问题吗
Now any questions?
可以给我们糖果了吗
Can we have our candy now?
想要糖果很简单
Just as soon as we go over
先重复一遍回去后要跟爸妈说的话
what you're gonna tell your parents.
-我们的风格是什么 -战前工匠
- Now what was our style? - Pre-war craftsman.
好 很好 面积是多少平方英尺
Good, good. And how many square feet?
还没有要糖的捣蛋鬼上门吗
Still no trick-or-treaters?
-还没 -可能今年大家出门晚吧
- Not yet. - Well, maybe people are going out later this year.
大街上全是小孩
Well, the street's full of kids,
但他们都远远地避开我们家
but they're actively detouring around our house.
往前走
Move along.
谁要糖糖
Who wants some candy?
好多知名品牌
Plenty of name-brand...
-家庭友善型糖糖在这里 -那是圈套
- family-friendly candy right here. - Oh! It's a trap!
没有 我 哎呀 你呢
No. I--ooh, how about you? Hey--
你要糖糖吗 来嘛
You want some candy, right? Come on,
-拿糖糖 -妈 妈妈 她抓住我了
- have some candy! - Mom! Mommy, she's got me!
不是 我不是故意的
No, I don't-- I'm not trying--
-我的糖 -不要了
- My candy! - Just leave it!
杰 你得准备去米奇和小卡的派对了
Jay, you have to get ready for Mitch and Cam's party.
歌洛莉亚 你看我的皮肤是不是松了很多
Gloria, does my skin look looser to you?
什么
What?
或许我应该试试你的颈部紧致霜
Maybe I should try some of that fancy neck cream of yours.
你不是说那里面有什么钻石精华还是什么的
Don't you have some with specks of diamonds in it or something?
不给糖就捣乱
Trick-or-treat.
你俩连装扮服都没穿
You guys don't even have costumes.
我扮的是一副骨架
I'm a skeleton.
我扮的是一颗柠檬
And I'm--I'm a lemon.
你们玩不给糖就捣蛋也太超龄了吧
Aren't you too old to be trick-or-treating?
你一大把年纪生孩子不也超龄了吗
Aren't you too old to be having a baby?
你觉得好笑吗 柠檬
Ah, you find that funny, lemon?
还有更好笑的
Here's a better joke.
开门 开门 啥没了
Knock, knock. What's gone?
你们的糖糖
Your candy!
怎么了
What was that?
没礼貌的傻瓜 他们以为他们能...
Some rude dummies, that they think that they can--
好了 要冷静
All right, listen. Let's just calm down.
准备去参加派对
Get ready for the party.
冷什么静
Calm down what?
你也和曼尼一样觉得我脾气暴躁吗
You think I'm a hothead, like Manny?
没
No!
你有些情绪化 可能有点些易怒
You can be emotional. Volatile, maybe.
但远远算不上...
Still, that's a far cry from--
你们往老娘家扔鸡蛋
You put egg on my house,
你们是不想好了
I kill what you love!
精神病
psycho.
-豪华储物间 -是啊 没错
- Plush utility room? - Yeah, right.
我怎么没见着大套间
I know a hall closet when I see one.
就像你爹从来不撒谎似的
And your dad never lies?
你那给电器看病的老爹
What medical school
上的是什么医学院来着
did the great appliance doctor attend?
-迪尔加多 -不 是德卡斯
-Hey, Delgado. - Oh, no! Durkas!
只要让这把伞拥有玛丽·波平斯仙女的魔力
What I wouldn't give for this umbrella to have
我什么都愿意
Mary Poppins' powers.
但愿他没听见
Oh, I pray he didn't hear that.
听说你今天拉响了防火警报
Heard you pulled the fire alarm today
让我们逃掉了一场考试
and got us out of that test.
-干的不错 -谢谢夸奖 德卡斯先生
- Good job. - Thanks, Mr. Durkas.
知道吗 你以后不用那么称呼我了
You know what? You don't need to call me that anymore.
还有 我们大家八点钟在操场上集会
Anyway, we're all meeting at the playground at 8:00
然后出去玩 你想来就一起吧
And heading out, if you want to join.
你一定要去
You're totally going to that.
是嘛 那样可就毁了你好学生的美名了
Yeah, if you want to ruin your reputation.
你总算能和那些酷小孩一起玩了
You're finally gonna be in with the cool kids.
那样你周一就得在全校大会上
You need to talk at the school assembly on Monday
向全体老师道歉
and apologize to all the teachers.
老师 更像是政府企业中的寄生虫
Teachers. More like public sector parasites.
坚强点 曼尼
Be strong, Manny.
放聪明点 冒险 派对
Be smart. Adventures, parties.
少管所 心脏病
Juvie, heartache.
小美妞们
Girls!
但不是我们想要的那种
But not the kind we want.
那全都是我们想要的
They're all the kind we want.
德拉斯先...
Mr. Dur--
康纳德
Conrad!
拿一个 我是捐蛋人[卵子捐献者]
Take one. I'm an egg donor.
我也喜欢你的装扮 小卡 可爱的牛牛
I love your costume, too, Cam. Adora-bull.
谢谢 都是为了搞笑
Oh, well, thank you. It's all in fun.
我其实想穿比较紧身的装扮服
I half-wanted to wear something tighter.
-你懂的 我瘦了 -能看出来
- You know, I've been reducing. - I can see.
-你言不由衷啊 -没 我真看出来了
- Well, you say it like you can't. - No, no, no. I totally can.
震撼吧
Impressive, huh?
是 我 我得...
Yeah. I'm--I'm gonna...
-小卡 -怎么
- Hey, Cam. - Mm?
我听说你在我们的客人面前脱衣服
I'm hearing a rumor that you keep flashing our guests.
不是变态的啦
Oh, well, not in a perverted way.
我只是希望让大家看看我隐藏在
I just want people to see my body
这套烂装扮服下的苗条身材
under this stupid costume.
这理由跟真正露阴癖的说辞差不多
That's very close to what actual flashers say.
-爸爸 -等一下 宝贝
- Daddy? - Yeah, one second, honey.
我已经厌倦了不断赞美他人
I'm just tired of throwing out compliments
却一句好话也听不到
and not getting anything back.
我跟罗伯托说他的美黑做得很自然
I told Roberto his spray tan looked real.
你自己看 把我们家枕头和猫都染黑了
Look for yourself. It's on two of our pillows and our cat.
爹地 怎么了
Daddy. Yeah?
看 那是我妈咪 她来了
Lookit. It's my mommy. She came.
不 宝贝 那不是你妈咪
Oh. Oh, no, honey, that's not your mommy.
不是吗
It's not?
不是的 那只是爸爸的一个朋友
No, no. That's just one of daddy's friends.
-什么情况 -没什么
- What's going on? - Oh, nothing.
她只是想吃蛋糕了
She just wants one of these cupcakes.
-但我已经吃过... -给你吃 宝贝
- But I already had... - Oh, there you go, honey.
好了 去吧 去交朋友 交起来
Okay, off you go. Mingle! Mingle!
看来有人来过了
Looks like some people came by.
是的 没错 有好几个人呢
Yeah. Oh, yeah, we had a few.
我看到你给踢下去了
I saw that.
你好
Hello?
嘿 亲爱的
Hey, honey.
你的开放参观搞得怎样
Hi. How's your open house?
没什么人来 其实
Pretty empty, actually.
我把气撒在一个
I kind of just took it out
扮成哈利·波特的孩子身上了
on a Harry Potter.
不过说真的 格兰芬多的学生
Seriously, though, a Gryffindor
怎么会让他妈帮他拿魁地奇飞天扫帚
letting his mom carry his Quidditch broom?
那有多赫奇帕奇作风啊
How Hufflepuff is that?
我这里也很凄凉
It's pretty lonely here, too.
我们被所有邻居列入黑名单了
We have been shunned by the whole neighborhood.
太荒谬了
That's ridiculous.
就因为你那个温柔的小把戏吗
All over some mild little gag you pulled?
那并不温柔 都有人来调查...
It was not mild. There was an investig...
我想我听到有人进来
Oh, I-I thought I heard someone.
可能只是树枝敲得窗户响
I guess it was just trees tapping against the window.
在这陈旧得格格直响的房子里真恐怖
It's pretty creepy over here in this rattly old house.
总之 我可能再呆半小时
Anyway, I'll probably give it another 30 minutes,
然后就回去了
then I'll see you at home.
好的 再见
Okay. Bye.
你笑什么呢
What are you laughing about?
笑你可怜的老爸 你懂的
Oh, it's just your poor dad, you know.
你可怜的傻老爸
Your poor, dumb dad.
我明天员工大会上再告诉你
I'll fill you in at the staff meeting
不过先得等克莱利说完他早晨上班路上的事
after Keneally's done telling us about his morning commute.
太逗了 你学他学得真像
That's hilarious! You sound just like him.
圣诞才艺表演时你一定得来一段
You are so doing that at Christmas talent night.
哥们 《千金小姐》 《莎拉的微笑》
Dude, "Rich Girl", "Sara Smile"...
以及返场的《少男杀手》
then a "Maneater" Encore.
他们简直棒得可怕
It was scary how good they were.
闭上眼睛听 跟真的乐队演唱一样
Close your eyes, it could have been the real band.
他赌球时走运了那么一次
Yeah, he got lucky in the football pool once,
现在就要加倍下赌注了
and now he wants to double the stakes.
我好怕怕
Oh, I'm so scared!
有没有
Right?
今晚弱爆了
Well, this night was a bust.
一个人都没有...
not a single person even...
还是我过早断言了
Or did I speak too soon?
有人想扮坏小艳鬼了吗
Was someone in the mood to be a bad little ghoul?
康尼 我不是说你
Oh, Connie, I didn't mean you.
我 那 那只是离婚的事影响了你
I'm...hey, that's just...that's just the divorce talking.
坚持住
Hang in there.
再见
Bye-bye.
看来某人终于决定变装成
Well, someone decided to take a trip
《梦幻岛》里的人物了
to Fantasy Island after all.
我好讨厌人们注意不到我全新曼妙的体形
Well, I'm tired of people not noticing my new physique.
要是这还不成 我就穿上尿布
If this doesn't work, I'm breaking out the diaper
戴上大礼帽扮作新年宝宝 你好
and top hat and going as Baby New Year! Hello.
天呐
Oh, my god!
囧囧 是你吗
John-John, is that you?
-你看起来太棒了 -谢谢
- You look amazing. - Thanks!
减掉一百磅 身材自然棒
That's what happens when you lose 100 pounds.
靠 他个小贱...
Oh, come on. What a...
-谁想举我 -我
- Who wants to lift me? - Me.
拜托 他怎么能不打电话就过来呢
Come on. How could he have not called us?
天呐 他轻得像羽毛一样
Oh, my god, he's as light as a feather.
你猜怎么着 我要去举举他
You know what? I'm gonna go lift him
然后晃到他手术钉都爆出来[缩胃手术]
and shake him till his staples pop.
小卡 别这样
Cam, stop!
我只是说我们原本可以抓住那两个小子
Just saying that we could have caught those kids.
怎么着 要追着他们跑一晚上吗
What, and chase them around all night?
我不是个年轻小伙子了
I'm not a young man anymore,
世人都不断提醒我那一点
as the world keeps pointing out.
刚刚外面那个服务生叫你什么
What did that waiter just call you outside?
中世纪的科尼尔
Medieval Knievel.
好好笑哦
That is hilarious.
我喜欢人们在装扮上花心思
I love when people put some thought into their outfit.
你是非法外星人 我是甜爹
Illegal Alien, Sugar Daddy.
你为什么说"非法"
Why do you say "illegal"?
因为戴着天线代表外星人 而你是...
Because antennas are alien, and you're...
怎样 非法移民吗
What? Illegal?
就因为我的肤色吗
Because of the color of my skin?
我干脆把你的宝宝扔进这煤气罐里吧
Why don't I dump your baby in your gas tank?
歌洛莉亚 别这样 请别介意
Gloria! Uh, no hard feelings, please.
尽情享受你的派对 好吗
Just enjoy the party, okay?
首先 放轻松 我们在派对上呢
First of all, relax. We're at a party.
其次 你已经被驱逐出境两次
Secondly, you've been deported twice.
你不能再这么敏感了
You're not allowed to be that defensive.
我最近是怎么了
What is it with me lately?
曼尼是对的 我真是个暴脾气
Manny's right. I'm such a hothead.
这是难免的 你怀孕了
It happens. You're pregnant.
就是这个原因 对吗
That's what it is, isn't it?
因为这个宝宝 他在里面生闷气
It's the baby. It's angry in there.
-不是的 -就是
- No! - Yes!
你刚刚自己说的 我变了
You just said it yourself. I have changed.
我肚子里有个愤怒的娃 逼着我干坏事
I have an angry baby inside of me making me do bad things!
荷尔蒙而已
It's just hormones.
是你的熊妈妈本能在发作
It's your mama bear instinct kicking in.
不是什么坏事
And that's a good thing,
因为这说明你会是一个好母亲 第二次
because that means you're gonna be a great mom--again.
你真这么想
Do you really think so?
你肚里的娃真幸运
You got a lucky little kid in there.
他的妈妈可不会让任何人伤害他
He's got a mom who's not gonna let anyone harm him.
或她
Or her.
希望是儿子
Or--or him.
不给糖果就捣蛋
Trick-or-treat.
去吧
Go ahead.
你们最好跑快点
You better run!
我的天呐
Oh, my gosh,
看看多萌啊
Is that the most precious thing you've ever seen?
我的天
Oh, my god.
你还认识其他公主吗
Do you know other princesses?
相信我 我认识一大堆呢
Trust me. I know lots.
好了 该睡觉了
Okay. Bedtime.
别 没那么晚
Oh, no, it's not that late.
你认识我妈妈吗 她就是个公主
Do you know my mom? She's a princess.
她累坏了
She's exhausted.
说胡话呢 她太累了
She's not making sense. She's so tired.
爸爸 是你跟我说的
Daddy, you told me!
她说什么呢 米奇尔
What is she talking about, Mitchell?
我的亲身母亲 她是公主 对吧
My real mom. She is, right?
好了 我想我们需要谈谈
Okay, I think we need to have a little talk.
萨姆 注意到小卡变苗条了没
Sam, do you notice how slim Cam's getting?
少来 等我回来再听你的回答
Nice try. I will be back for that answer.
没用的 克莱尔
This isn't gonna work, Claire...
我知道你在这儿
'cause I know you're here.
打算怎么吓我呀
What's the plan, anyway?
冷不丁蹦出来吗
You gonna pop out at me?
要想吓到我这还差得远
It's gonna take more than that to scare this--
-有人吗 -嗨
- Hello?! - Hi!
还能看房吗
Is the house still open?
能 是的 我马上下来
Oh, yes! Yes! I'll be right down.
克莱尔 别闹了 我有工作
Claire, this is serious! I have a job!
并不是说你没工作 你全年无休
Not that you don't. You work 24/7
得到的回报远少于付出的
and you don't get half the appreciation you deserve.
但我们能过会再说不
Can we talk about this later?
如你们潜在买家所见
As you potential buyers can see,
这是 一座漂亮的房子
This is a, uh, a beautiful home.
这后面是什么
What's behind here?
是我就不过去
Oh, I wouldn't go in there!
除非你们喜欢正式餐厅
Unless you love formal dining rooms.
-亲爱的 瞧瞧这个 -在厨房呢
- Honey, look at this. - I'm in the kitchen.
我们最好呆在一起
Oh, we should probably stay together.
赶紧的 希拉
Come on, Sheila.
-菲尔 问个问题 这些是 -等等
- Phil, one question. Are these-- - Wait, wait.
我超爱看人们的反应
I just love to see people's reactions
当我向他们展示
When I show them--
如此大的存储空间 靠 太疯狂了
So much storage. What? It's crazy!
我想你们会发现这所房子
I think you guys will find that this house
惊喜重重
is full of so many... delightful surprises
你们会很高兴...
That you'll be happy here for--
-我的天呐 -那人我不认识
- Oh, my god! - I don't know her!
这是原装浴缸吗
Is this the original tub?
什么 是的
What? Yes, it is.
它是 原装浴缸
It is, uh, the original tub.
原始夹具 斜面镜
Um, original fixtures, beveled mirror,
有个宽敞的淋浴隔间就足够了
Just a-a huge stall shower.
如果你们将 想搞个派对的话
If you guys would, uh, want to have a party.
我开玩笑呢
I'm kidding, of course.
这是座 个性鲜明的房子
But, um, just a house with a real personality.
我们马上就来 甜心
We'll be right in, sweetie.
我们说好要一起告诉莉莉她娘的事
We agreed to tell Lily about her mother together,
一起穿着大地色有镇静作用的衣服
wearing calming earth tones,
而且我们说好要告诉她真相的
and we agreed to tell her the truth.
我知道 但难道你就从没向莉莉说过
I know, but haven't you ever said something dumb to Lily
任何希望她转眼忘掉的蠢话
that you wish she would just forget?
别扯上我 赶紧解决这事吧
This isn't about me. Let's just fix this.
好的 挺好 但是...
Okay, great. Although...
你答应得如此爽快让我不得不怀疑
the way you agreed so quickly makes me wonder
你又对莉莉说过些什么
what sort of things you've told her.
我可能告诉过她说谎会害死小鸟
I may have told her her fibs kills birds.
你真行 等下再来谈这事
Wow. We're coming back to that one.
嗨 公主
Oh, hi, princess.
乖女儿 能说个小话不
Hey, Lil. Could we talk to you for a second?
我闯祸了吗
Am I in trouble?
我的天 没有 当然不是 甜心
Oh, gosh, no. Of course not, sweetie.
你还记得我们过去老跟你说
Um... Well, do you remember how we used to tell you
枯萎的花会到达天堂的事吗
there was a heaven for all the flowers that die?
"过去老说"是神马意思
What do you mean, "used to"?
抱歉 说漏嘴鸟 过会儿再谈
Sorry, I let it slip. We'll deal with it later.
乃到底瞒着我多少事
Much much are you not telling me?
乃们为什么这么说话
Why are you talking like this?
爸爸们刚说岔了
Daddies took a little side trip.
-不好意思 甜心 -有时候
- Sorry, sweetie. - Um, so sometimes, uh,
我们说一些话只是想让你高兴
we tell you things like that to make you feel better.
当我告诉你你妈妈是公主时
And I might have done the same thing
也只是想让你高兴
when I told you that your mom is a princess.
那她不是公主
So she's not?
你知道吗
Well, you know what?
-她可能是 -可能是的
- She might be. - She might be.
但我们不能肯定 宝贝
But we can't know for sure, honey,
因为 我们不知道她在哪里
Because... well, we don't know where she is
或是 她在做什么
Or... what she's doing.
但我们知道的是
B-but what--what we do know
她非常非常爱你
is that she loved you very, very much...
她知道自己没法好好照顾你
And she knew that she couldn't take care of you,
所以她让你来到了
so she made sure that you went
她能找到的最有爱的家庭
with the most loving family she could find.
所以我们三个人组成了一个家
And that's how the three of us became a family.
这样说你能接受吗 亲爱的
Does that make sense, sweetie?
你有问题要问我们吗
Do you have any questions for us?
你们为什么要说谎 害死一只鸟
Why did you say a fib and kill a bird?
我刚才注意到你和你太太一起来的
I noticed you walking in with your wife earlier.
她好漂亮
She's stunning.
知道你这句恭维话里我最喜欢什么吗
You know my favorite part of that compliment?
你认为她是我太太
You knew she was my wife.
全世界一半的人认为她是我女儿
Half the world thinks she's my daughter.
要我说 幸运的是她
Well, if you ask me, she's a lucky girl.
对我来说就不幸了
Bummer for me, though.
大帅哥在这里 却已经名草有主了
Handsomest man in here, and he's taken.
我敢肯定你的追求者不少
I'll bet you do all right with the boys.
的确
I do.
而我感兴趣的是你
It's the men I'm interested in.
看来你是个直抒胸臆的人啊
You just put it all right out there, don't you?
我倒是想约束一下我的"凶器"[男根]
I always try to hold a little something back.
我的天
Oh, my gosh.
别过去 别管他们
No, no, no, no, no, no. Leave him.
-可你知道这是... -知道 他需要这个
- No, but you know that's a-- - I know. He needs this.
好吧
Okay.
-很高兴认识你 杰 -我也是 萨姆
- It was great meeting you, Jay. - You, too, Sam.
哇 看来某人很喜欢你啊
Wow! Looks like somebody really likes you.
我能说什么呢 魅力不减当年啊
What can I say? I still got it.
我一直想问你 你瘦身了吗
I've been meaning to ask you-- have you lost some weight?
-你看起来棒极了 -你不知道
- Because you look good. - Wow, you have no idea
你这句话对我来说多重要 杰
what that means to hear from you, Jay.
抱那边
Uh, turn it that way.
我觉得这样会让你开心起来
I thought this might cheer you up.
灰机 灰机
Da plane! Da plane!
宝贝女儿
Baby girl!
瞧你 连经典词都教给她了
Look you! You even taught her the catchphrase.
杰 来见见我的新"纹身"
Yeah. Jay, have you seen my new tattoo?
-再联系 -多谢前来
- Be in touch. - Well, thanks so much for coming.
-多谢 -客气了
- Yeah. Thanks. - Okay.
克莱尔 他们走了 你可以出来了
Okay, Claire, they're gone. You can come out now.
克莱尔
Claire?
亲爱的 很抱歉我之前说你不吓人
Honey, I'm sorry I said you weren't scary.
今天太累了
It's been such a long day.
我们回家好吗
Can we please just go home?
好了 我自己走咯
All right. I'm leaving without ya.
看来 你会用这个遥控器啊
So... this remote you know how to use.
喂
Yes?
菲尔 你在哪里
Phil, where are you?
克莱尔 你在哪里
Claire? Where are you?
我过去吓你 但听到你带那对夫妻
I came over to scare you, but then I heard you
参观房子
showing the house to that couple,
所以我就没妨碍你
so I got out of your way.
你在家里吗
Are you at home?
是 我十分钟前就回来了
Yeah. I got here ten minutes ago.
那 那你是说
S-so... So you're saying...
这通电话不是从这间房子里打来的
This call isn't coming from inside the house?
你说什么呢 快回家吧
What are you talking about? Just get home.
孩子们和我都饿了
The kids and I are hungry.
快点 爸
Yeah, hurry up, dad.
我们想你
We miss you!
我也想你 小老弟
Miss you, too, buddy.
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick-or-treat!
其实我也没那么害怕啦
I wasn't really that scared.
好吧怕死了
Okay.
你还没说你有没有用蛋砸到那些小子
Hey, you never told me if you hit those kids with that egg.
他们混进了人群
They blended into the crowd,
但有个动作慢的
but there was a slow one with them.
他跑不快
He couldn't run so fast,
所以我好好地用蛋给他洗了下
and I nailed him pretty good.
-我警告过你的 -好啦 罗本
- I warned you. - Okay, Reuben.
你那些酷朋友现在去哪里了
Where are your cool friends now?
没用棉签替你清洗耳朵 这是肯定的
Not q-tipping your ear, that's for sure.
得了 罗本
Okay, Reuben.
这就是我不和酷孩子混在一起的原因
This is why I never hang out with cool kids.
是啊 是你拒绝了他们
Yeah, you rejected them,
就在你和你妈在达人秀上
Shortly after you and your mom
表演滚轴溜冰舞之后
roller danced at the talent show.
我家被烧了缺钱
Oh... we were robbed.
反正跟你们选的歌一点关系都没有
Couldn't have been the song you picked.
《翼下之风》 痛
"Wind beneath my w--" Ow!